{ // Topic: Requirement Elicitation
  "Question 1": {
    "question": "What is the first step of requirement elicitation?", // Easy
    "answer1": "Identifying stakeholders", 
    "answer2": "Listing out requirements",
    "answer3": "Requirements gathering",
    "answer4": "Verification of requirements",
    "cor_answer": "Identifying stakeholders"
  },
  "Question 2": {
    "question": "What is a project mission statement?", // Medium
    "answer1": "A complex piece of document which state the steps required to complete the project",
    "answer2": "A document which must define the stakeholders, developers and can be ambiguous",
    "answer3": "A simple short statement of what companies intend to accomplish in the project", 
    "answer4": "A statement which states what the project is about and its stakeholders",
    "cor_answer":  "A simple short statement of what companies intend to accomplish in the project"
  },
  "Question 3": {
    "question": "Which of the following is an example of Non-Functional Requirement?", // Hard
    "answer1": "The bank customer must be able to withdraw cash from the ATM",
    "answer2": "The system must be able to use WiFi to communicate all transactions with a clients secure database",
    "answer3": "The customer must be able to load the webpage within 3 seconds", 
    "answer4": "The system must display the current time in 24 hour format",
    "cor_answer": "The customer must be able to load the webpage within 3 seconds"
  }
  "Question 4": {
    "question": "Which of the following is true about Atomic Requirement?", // Medium
    "answer1": "The requirement is readable and easily understood by others",
    "answer2": "The requirement is verifiable, traceable and unambiguous", 
    "answer3": "The atomic requirement is elicited only by the design team",
    "answer4": "The terms used in the requirement must be consistent and complex",
    "cor_answer": "The requirement is verifiable, traceable and unambiguous"
  }
  "Question 5": {
    "question": "Which of the following is an example of Atomic Requirement?", // Boss?
    "answer1": "The user interface must be user-friendly",
    "answer2": "The time taken to search for a query must be fast",
    "answer3": "The system must be able to support a minimum number of 10 users concurrently at any given time", 
    "answer4": "The system must not crash easily when there is a heavy load",
    "cor_answer": "The system must be able to support a minimum number of 10 users concurrently at any given time"
  }
  "Question 6": {
    "question": "Why is Requirement Elicitation a difficult task?", // Easy
    "answer1": "Problem of understanding the requirement",
    "answer2": "Problem of the scope",
    "answer3": "Problem of volatility",
    "answer4": "All of the above",
    "cor_answer" : "All of the above"
  },
  "Question 7": {
    "question": "What is an actor in a use case?", // Easy
    "answer1": "A person who is a stakeholder in the system's design",
    "answer2": "A person who design the system",
    "answer3": "Any person who might use the system",
    "answer4": "A person or external system that interacts with the system",
    "cor_answer": "A person or external system that interacts with the system"
  },
  "Question 8": {
    "question": "Which of the following is true about <<include>> in the Use Case Diagram", // Hard
    "answer1": "It helps to add more functionality to another use case",
    "answer2": "It is only used in parent Use Case in exceptional or unusual circumstances",
    "answer3": "It supports the reuse of functionality in a Use Case model", 
    "answer4": "The included use case is usually optional",
    "cor_answer": "It supports the reuse of functionality in a Use Case model"
  }
  "Question 9": {
    "question": "A Use Case description MUST include which of the following:", // Medium
    "answer1": "Participating Actors", <-
    "answer2": "Frequency",
    "answer3": "Assumptions",
    "answer4": "Exceptions",
    "cor_answer": "Participating Actors"
  }
    "Question 10": {
    "question": "Which of the following is true about 'Flow of Events' in a Use Case description?", // Boss
    "answer1": "It shows the variations or errors in the interaction",
    "answer2": "It must include the exceptional situations that cause the failure of the Use Case",
    "answer3": "It shows the normal or main successful flow of the Use Case",
    "answer4": "It contains the alternate flow of the Use Case",
    "cor_answer": "It shows the normal or main successful flow of the Use Case"
  }
    "Question 11": {
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT true about the differences between Functional Requirements and Use Cases?", // Boss
    "answer1": "Functional Requirements are more focused on the User level while Use Cases are more focused on the Developer level",
    "answer2": "Functional Requirements state what is it about while Use Cases states how the functions interact",
    "answer3": "Functional Requirements show the overall Use Cases while Use Cases describe how a user uses a system to accomplish a goal", 
    "answer4": "Functional Requirements focus is on the written text while Use Cases focus is on the diagram itself",
    "cor_answer": "Functional Requirements show the overall Use Cases while Use Cases describe how a user uses a system to accomplish a goal"
  }
    "Question 12": {
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT the main reason why project team review clients specification?", // Hard
    "answer1": "To identify the actors in the Use Case",
    "answer2": "To initiate the generation of Data Dictionary",
    "answer3": "To ensure that the design of the system can be completed on schedule", 
    "answer4": "To identify uncertainties and clarify with client",
    "cor_answer": "To ensure that the design of the system can be completed on schedule"
  }
}